spb.com 2012-06-08

# Privacy Policy » SPB Software

Privacy Policy

## SPB Software Privacy Policy

SPB Software is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to data collected by SPB Software through the majority of its websites and services, as well as its offline product support services. It does not apply to those SPB Software sites, services and products that do not display or link to this statement or that have their own privacy statements.

### Changes

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it regularly. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy.

### Security

SPB Software uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.

### Cookies

SPB Software websites and services use "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server.

### Information Collection and Use

SPB Software requests and collects personal information like your name, address, telephone number, and email address. This can be done while you are visiting our forums, requesting support, and during the purchase process. We do not collect or save any credit card or other payment information. These information are only collected by our payment partners like Handango.com, Handster.com, and others. We do not have access to these information. We also track user traffic throughout our websites and services. We use this tracking information to optimize our websites and services and to make aggregate reports on traffic for our partners.

The information that we collect is necessary for us to fulfill your order, track the status of your order, and provide the best possible customer service. SPB Software from time to time, send newsletters and notices of special offers and product discounts. From time to time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our websites.

We will not give or sell your private information to any outside company for its use in marketing or solicitation. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

Some SPB Software websites and services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If you register for or use such services, both SPB Software and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services.

|     
---|---
